export const pptQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Which view shows all slides as thumbnails?",
    options: ["Slide Sorter", "Slide Show", "Normal", "Notes Page"],
    answer: "Slide Sorter",
  },
  {
    question: "Which shortcut starts the slideshow from the beginning?",
    options: ["F5", "Ctrl + F5", "Shift + F5", "Alt + F5"],
    answer: "F5",
  },
  {
    question: "Which file extension is used for PowerPoint presentations?",
    options: [".ppt", ".pptx", ".pps", ".pptm"],
    answer: ".pptx",
  },
  {
    question: "Which feature adds movement to objects on slides?",
    options: ["Animation", "Transition", "Slide Show", "Effect"],
    answer: "Animation",
  },
  {
    question: "Which option controls slide change effects?",
    options: ["Animation", "Transition", "Slide Master", "Design"],
    answer: "Transition",
  },
  {
    question: "Which key is used to move to the next slide in slideshow?",
    options: ["Enter", "N", "Right Arrow", "All of the above"],
    answer: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    question: "Which view is best for editing slide content?",
    options: ["Slide Sorter", "Normal", "Reading View", "Notes Page"],
    answer: "Normal",
  },
  {
    question: "Which feature is used to manage slide layouts?",
    options: ["Slide Master", "Design", "Animation", "Transition"],
    answer: "Slide Master",
  },
  {
    question: "Which tab contains themes in PowerPoint?",
    options: ["Insert", "View", "Design", "Animations"],
    answer: "Design",
  },
  {
    question: "Which file format is used to save a slideshow with timings?",
    options: [".ppt", ".pptx", ".ppsx", ".pdf"],
    answer: ".ppsx",
  },
];
